

## **Profile Info**

I define myself as a front-end artist. I spend hours of my day researching and sharpening my knowledge considering that JS is a fast-improving language. Most of my researches is targeted to make life easier for my successors and chiefly end-users. So another example of the inner tension killing me is the word "Best Practice". Those who succeed are those who love their job. I love my job. I have a weighty knowledge and experience of versioning processes, releasing strategies, CSS, and JS best practices.

#### Language

Turkish Azerbaijani English Russian



### **Work Experience**

2019.1 - Present

#### Frontend Engineer

The Fabrika Bursa Turkey

2018.8 - 2019.1

#### Frontend Developer

UTC Agency Bursa Turkey



#### Frontend Developer

Nivelsoft Baku Azerbaijan

## **Projects**

# "Green Brown Coffee Mobile version" E-Commerce

(HTML, CSS, SCSS, JS, jQuery) mgreen.anarmamedov.com Jun 2022 - Sep 2022

#### "Green Brown Coffee" E-Commerce

(HTML, CSS, SCSS, JS, jQuery) green.anarmamedov.com Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

#### Zirve Office Furnitures E-commerce

(HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JS, jQuery) mobilyaci.anarmamedov.com Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

#### Netflix Clone Entertainment

(React js, MUI) projectwithreact.anarmamedov.com May 2022 - Jun 2022

# Aksu Municipality Association E-Commerce

(HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JS, jQuery) dernek.anarmamedov.com Dec 2021 - Jan 2022

# Faruk Çelik Former MP's Portfolio Page

(HTML, CSS, SCSS, JS, jQuery) project.anarmamedov.com Sep 2021 - Oct 2021

## My Reference

#### Mustafa Özdemir

Founder, The Fabrika Bursa - Turkey +90 506 780 0164

#### Kemal Findanboylu

Prof. Dr., Uludag University Bursa - Turkey +90 224 295 5282 kfidan@uludag.edu.tr

### Education

3

 $\boxtimes$ 

0

in

3

2018 - 2022 Bachelor`s Degree Computer Engineering Uludag University Bursa, Turkey

+90 507 653 46 41

Istanbul / Turkey

anarmamedov.com

anar.mammadov3@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/anar-mamedov

github.com/Anar-Mamedov

2017 - 2018 Bachelor`s Degree Computer Engineering Bulent Ecevit University Zonguldak, Turkey

2008 - 2012 Bachelor`s Degree International Relations Khazar University Baku, Azerbaijan

### Skills

- JavaScript
- ReactJS
- ReduxJS
- jQuery
- TypeScript
- HTML, CSS Preprocessors
- JSS / Styled-Components
- Bootstrap
- Material UI (MUI)
- Node.js (Express.js)
- Python
- UI Design Softwares

## **Certificates**

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
  2.03.2015 | from SKAY-LINE Course
- English Language Certificate 2013 - 2014 | from GRBS Course
- Organization for Security and Co-operation in Europe
   22.04.2012 | from OSCE Conference